Natdanai Thannin

Tel: +66-63-516-4850

Email: natdanaitnn@gmail.com
Alternate email: 678familyz@gmail.com
Portfolio Site: https://natdanai.vercel.app/

Skills: C++, C# .NET, PHP, JavaScript, Lua, Java, Python, React, Next.js, Svelte, Nest.js

A junior developer with 2 years of experience in frontend and backend developments who is passionate about working in any challenge opportunities. I spend every single day with coding and learning new programming languages and new technologies. I'm not afraid of any problems but I push my effort to solve them for being pleased with success and growing up with failure.

Experiences

FIVEM FREELANCE (2021- present)

Developer

- Developed game play by Lua and Javascript (typescript).
- Implemented user interface with Svelte, React and Next.js.
- Designed the database table on MYSQL.
- Developed in-game music from YouTube for player by using google API.
- Developed server monitoring and notification via Discord by using Discord Api.
- Developed event driven system in backend for communicating between client and server.
- Developed cheating protection by XOR encryption.
- Developed authentication system by using UUID for user identity.
- Developed FiveM website and backend api by using next.js.
- Developed usage transaction and historical enquiry system.
- Developed time synchronization between website and server.
- Developed game top up system.

Icon Framework (2020 - 2021)

Intern Developer

- Developed and maintained e-Property system by using C# and ASP.NET connecting to MSSQL.
- Enhanced the system to collect information of maintenance fee's payment transaction and key card transaction.
- Developed an internal system for inhouse project contained multi-functions such as ticket tracking, project's cost calculation, project member maintenance and time management by using React.js, Nest.js and MSSQL.

Education

Bachelor's Degree of Information Technology | 2017 - 2021

King Mongkut's University of Technology North Bangkok

Senior Project: Medical System for PrachinBuri Provincial Public Health Office | 2021

Programming Language: PHP

- Developed an application for stock checking, herbal disbursing, and medical disbursement.
- Developed administrator system for maintaining and monitoring.
- Developed partner's order tracking and notification system for medical expiration and order alert for making new purchase order to partner.
- Developed reports enquiry system for disbursing, importing, stock remaining and best seller.

Certificate

React 15 Workshop (Building 15 Projects) on udemy

Issued march 2023 (No expiration date)

Typescript on udemy

Issued march 2023 (No expiration date)